So Mr. Popper doesn't know what Mr. Tanaka really is, does he?
That's right. I think that's probably true.
He has no intention of revealing it.
That's interesting.
Don't you think that's enough?
I get that a lot. They think I'm a staple.
A star prostitute?
I don't think so,
But when I say "caw", it's a false "caw".
Really?
That's amazing.
Nighttime and Idol
Well, here I am, the sugar-fed kettle boy from Stardaxxo.
And now, let's welcome today's guest, Mr. Idol.
I'm Saho Tanaka from Crown Pop, and I'm here to grab your wolf.
I'm Saho Tanaka from CrownePop, how do you do?
Thank you very much.
I have the impression that you have a lot of movement in each of your kassans.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I was just saying that I'm looking forward to working with you today.
I'm sorry, I'm a little shy around cameras.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't take my eyes off of you from beginning to end.
Thank you very much.
Not only when he sings, but also when he talks.
I think you are quite unique.
I don't think there are many like her.
Really?
Well, I'd like to follow up on that in a little more depth.
The other day, you and Negishi-san went on a pilgrimage to a sacred place for anime on this program.
What is your favorite genre of anime, Mr. Tanaka?
I don't know... anime, like idols or Love Live.
Zombieland Saga, a story about a zombie girl who becomes an idol, or something like that.
I also like comedies.
You compare yourself with idols because I'm an idol myself, so it's hard for me to compare myself with idols.
But I'm an idol geek myself, so I tend to look at it from the geek side.
I'm just trying to do my best.
Did you go to a lot of shows?
Well, I was the kind of kid who couldn't really tell my parents or anyone that I wanted to go to live shows.
But you're not very good at talking about how you feel, and yet you're always talking about what you want to do.
That's probably where it started.
I'm sorry, I'm a little curious about the opening.
Did you get into this agency through a scout?
But I wanted to try this kind of work.
I can say I want to do something if I'm asked to do it, but...
I'm not good at finding something on my own and saying, "I'd like to try this.
I see.
But now, do you still want to do something?
Well, yes.
It's hard to say here.
Here's the place.
I'd like to do something like this.
But I can't say it unless I'm in the right mood.
I can't say it unless I'm in the mood.
There are people who can say what they want to do if they say it out loud.
But if you don't...
I only say things when I'm in the right mood.
That's how it is.
I don't know, it's difficult.
You don't know what Mr. Tanaka really is, do you, Mr. Popper?
Yes, I think you're probably right.
And you don't intend to reveal it.
That's interesting.
Then what do you think Mr. Popper would say about you, Mr. Tanaka?
I wonder.
I'm sure they'd say, "I like this part of you.
I wonder... everyone says I'm so cute and pretty.
How do you feel when you hear that?
It makes me happy to hear people say I'm cute, whether it's in words or in letters.
You're the most interesting person on the staff, Mr. Tanaka.
I'm glad we could talk today.
It might be a bit of a corner to say that I can do pretty much anything, but I can do anything.
I see, you can do anything.
This program is...
Mr. Pierre
Kazuo Sagami
Mr. Namu
Mr. Jaboten
Mr. Nickname Naji
Thank you very much for providing us with this information!
Thank you very much for providing us!
Please look again next time!
See you soon!